Finding Aid for Office of the Vice President for Research (University of Michigan), Records, 1950-2001
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Charles G. Overberger/Alfred S. Sussman Series
  - Topical File (), 1966-1985; primarily 1982-1984
    - Energy Cost Avoidance Project (ECAP), 1984 (Box 76)
    - Energy Research Advisory Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 76)
    - Energy Research, Office of, 1982-1984; 2 folders (Box 76)
    - Engineering, College of, 1982-1984; 3 folders (Box 76)
    - Engineering Research Center (Kan Chen, Director), 1982-1984 (Box 76)
    - English Composition Board, 1979-1984 (Box 76)
    - English Department of, 1982-1984 (Box 76)
    - English Language Institute, 1982 (Box 76)
    - Enrollments, 1982-1983 (Box 76)
    - Environmental and Industrial Health, Institute of, 1982-1984 (Box 76)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1982-1984 (Box 76)
    - Environmental Research Institute of Michigan (ERIM), 1983 (Box 76)
    - Epidemiology, Department of, 1981-1984 (Box 76)
    - Equipment Needs Survey, 1983-1984 (Box 76)
    - Equipment, University Research, 1983-1984 (Box 77)
    - Export Control, 1982 (Box 77)
      (see also Federal Legislative Advisory Group)
    - Extension Services, 1983-1984 (Box 77)
    - Eye Center, 1982-1983 (Box 77)
    - E General, 1982-1984 (Box 77)
    - Faculty, 1982-1984 (Box 77)
    - Faculty, Economic Status of, 1981-1982 (Box 77)
    - Federal Legislative Action Group (FLAG), 1983-1984 (Box 77)
      (see also Export Control)
    - Financial Aid, Office of, 1981-1984 (Box 77)
    - Flint Campus, UM, 1981-1984 (Box 77)
    - Food and Drug Administration (FDA), 1982 (Box 77)
    - Football Luncheons, 1982 (Box 77)
    - Freedom of Information Act, 1982 (Box 77)
    - F General, 1982-1984 (Box 77)
    - General Counsel, Office of the, 1981-1984 (Box 77)
    - Geological Sciences, 1982-1984 (Box 77)
    - Gerontology, Institute of, 1982-1984 (Box 77)
    - Getty Postdoctoral Fellowships in the History of Art, 1984 (Box 77)
    - Gifts (Bequests for Research), 1983-1984 (Box 77)
    - Government Relations, Council on, 1982-1984; 2 folders (Box 77)
    - Graduate School (Rackham), 1982-1984 (Box 77)
    - Graduate Student Aid, Task Force on, 1983 (Box 77)
    - Graduate Student Assistance, 1984 (Box 77)
    - Great Lakes and Marine Waters Center, 1982-1984; 2 folders (Box 77)
    - Great Lakes Trade Adjustment Assistance Center, 1983 (Box 77)
    - Group Dynamics, Center for, 1982-1983 (Box 77)
    - G General, 1982-1984 (Box 77)
    - Hazardous Waste Research Center, 1982-1984 (Box 77)
    - Higher Education, Center for the Study of, 1982 (Box 77)
    - History, Department of, 1982-1983 (Box 77)
    - Hospital, UM Replacement, 1983 (Box 77)
    - Human Genetics, 1982-1984 (Box 77)
    - Human Growth and Development, Center for, 1982-1984 (Box 77)
    - H General, 1982-1984 (Box 77)
    - Indirect Costs, 1982-1984; 3 folders (Box 78)
    - Indirect Costs, Monto Report, 1983 (Box 78)
    - Industrial and Operations Engineering, 1982-1984 (Box 78)
    - Industrial Development Division (IST), 1982-1984 (Box 78)
    - Industry/University Relations, 1982-1984; 3 folders (Box 78)
    - Information Services, 1982-1984 (Box 78)
    - Inquiries and Miscellaneous Questions, 1982-1984 (Box 78)
    - Institutional Cooperation, Committee on (CIC), 1982-1984 (Box 78)
    - Intellectual Properties Counsel, 1983-1984 (Box 78)
    - Intellectual Properties, Policy on (By-law 3.10), 1979 (Box 78)
    - Internal Medicine, Department of, 1982-1984 (Box 78)
    - International Business Machines (IBM), 1984 (Box 78)
    - I General, 1982-1985 (Box 78)
    - Japanese Studies, Center for, 1982-1984 (Box 78)
    - Kelsey Museum, 1983-1984 (Box 78)
    - Kimberly-Clark, 1982 (Box 78)
    - KMS Fusion, 1981-1982 (Box 78)
    - K General, 1982-1984 (Box 78)
    - Labor and Industrial Relations, Institute of (ILIR), 1982-1984 (Box 78)
    - Laboratory Animal Medicine (ULAM), 1982-1984; 3 folders
      - ULAM, Committee on Use and Care of Animals, 1981-1985; 2 folders (Box 78)
    - Law School, 1982-1984 (Box 78)
    - Library Science, School of, 1982-1984 (Box 78)
    - Literature, Science, and the Arts, College of, 1982-1984 (Box 78)
    - MacArthur Foundation (John O. and Catherine T.), 1984 (Box 79)
    - Macromolecular Research Center, 1977-1984 (Box 79)
    - Markley, Lucille P., Charitable Trust, 1984 (Box 79)
    - Materials and Metallurgical Engineering, Department of, 1982-1984 (Box 79)
    - Mathematics, Department of, 1982-1984 (Box 79)
    - Mechanical Engineering and Applied Mechanics, Department of, 1982-1983 (Box 79)
    - Medical School, 1982-1984; 3 folders (Box 79)
    - Medical Science Research Building, 1981-1982 (Box 79)
    - Megaproposals (UM generated research initiatives on grand scale), 1984 (Box 79)
    - Mental Health Research Institute, 1982-1984 (Box 79)
    - MERIT (Michigan Education of Resources and Informational Triad), 1982-1984
      - General, 1982-1984 (Box 79)
      - Board of Directors, 1982-1984; 3 folders (Box 79)
    - Michigan Energy and Resource Research Association (MERRA), 1982-1984 (Box 79)
    - Michigan Historical Collections (Bentley), 1982-1984 (Box 79)
    - Michigan Interuniversity Committee on Information Systems (MICIS), 1984 (Box 79)
    - Michigan Molecular Institute, 1984 (Box 79)
    - Michigan Research Corporation, 1982-1986; 4 folders (Box 79)
    - Michigan Scientist of the Year Nomination, 1983-1986 (Box 80)
    - Michigan Sea Grant, 1983-1984
      - Policy Committee, 1982-1984; 2 folders (Box 80)
      - Program, 1982-1985; 2 folders (Box 80)
      - Site Visit, 1981-1982 (Box 80)
    - Michigan Society for Medical Research, 1982-1984 (Box 80)
    - Michigan, State of
      - Governor, 1981-1985 (Box 80)
      - Governor's Commission on Higher Education, 1983-1984 (Box 80)
      - Governor's Committee on High Technology, 1981-1984 (Box 80)
      - Hazardous Waste Management Committee, 1983 (Box 80)
      - Legislature, 1981-1983 (Box 80)
      - Mindpower Conference, 1981-1982 (Box 80)
      - Public Health, Department of, 1982-1983 (Box 80)
    - Michigan State University, 1982-1983 (Box 80)
    - Michigan Student Assembly, 1982-1984 (Box 80)
    - Michigan Technology Council, 1982-1984 (Box 80)
    - Microbiology and Immunology, Department of, 1982-1984 (Box 80)
    - Middle English Dictionary, 1978-1984
      - Jim Downer/Raymond Page, Co-Editors, Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 80)
    - Midwest Universities Energy Consortium (MUEC), 1982-1984 (Box 80)
    - Molecular Beam Epitavy System, 1983 (Box 80)
    - Molecular Genetics, 1981-1984; 3 folders (Box 80)
    - Music, School of, 1982-1984 (Box 81)
    - M General, 1982-1984 (Box 81)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1982-1983 (Box 81)
    - National Institute of Health, 1982-1984
      - Bio/medical Research Support Grants (BRSG), 1982-1984 (Box 81)
    - National Medal of Science, 1981-1983 (Box 81)
    - National Science Board, 1982-1983 (Box 81)
    - National Science Foundation, 1982-1984 (Box 81)
    - Natural Resources, School of, 1982-1984 (Box 81)
    - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering, 1982-1983 (Box 81)
    - Navy, Department of, 1982-1983 (Box 81)
    - Neuroscience Laboratory, 1982-1984
      - General, 1982-1984 (Box 81)
    - Building Executive Committee Minutes, 1982-1984 (Box 81)
    - Building Review Committee, 1977-1982 (Box 81)
    - Building Review Committee Vitae, 1982-1983 (Box 81)
    - Neurosurgical Head Protection Program, 1982-1984 (Box 81)
    - Nuclear Engineering, Department of, 1982-1984 (Box 81)
    - Nuclear Medicine, 1982-1984 (Box 81)
    - Nuclear Free Zone Proposal, 1983-1984; 2 folders (Box 81)
    - Nuclear Regulatory Commission, 1981-1983 (Box 82)
      - Civil Penalty ($1500) imposed, September, 1982; 1981-1982; 2 folders (Box 82)
    - Nursing, School of, 1982-1984 (Box 82)
    - Nutrition Research, Advisory Committee on, 1981 (Box 82)
    - N General, 1982-1984 (Box 82)
    - Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1982-1984 (Box 82)
    - Occupational Safety and Environmental Health, Department of, 1982-1984 (Box 82)
    - Ophthalmology, Department of, 1982-1983 (Box 82)
    - Orphan Disease Treatment Research Center, 1982-1984 (Box 82)
    - O General, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
    - Patent Policy, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
    - Patients (Miscellaneous Individuals), 1982-1984; 2 folders (Box 82)
    - Pediatrics, Department of, 1982-1984 (Box 82)
    - Personnel, Department of, 1982-1984 (Box 82)
    - Pharmacology, 1982-1984 (Box 82)
    - Pharmacy, College of, 1982-1984 (Box 82)
    - Phoenix Project, Michigan Memorial, 1980-1984; 2 folders (Box 82)
    - Physical Education, Department of, 1984 (Box 82)
    - Physics, Department of, 1981-1982; 2 folders (Box 82)
    - Physics, Department of, 1983-1984; 3 folders (Box 83)
    - Physiology, Department of, 1983-1984 (Box 83)
    - Plant Extension Committee, 1980-1984 (Box 83)
    - Political and Social Research, Inter-University Consortium for, 1982-1984 (Box 83)
    - Political Science, Department of, 1981-1983 (Box 83)
    - Political Studies, Center for, 1982-1984 (Box 83)
    - Population Planning, Center for, 1983 (Box 83)
    - Population Studies, Center for, 1982-1984 (Box 83)
    - Positions, Interested in, 1982-1984 (Box 83)
    - Position Emissions Tomography (PET Project), 1981-1984 (Box 83)
    - Postdoctoral Scholars Committee, 1980-1983 (Box 83)
    - President, University of Michigan, Office of, 1966-1985
      - Annual Reports to, 1981-1985; 2 folders (Box 83)
        (see Department files)
      - Annual Report to (from Office of Vice-President for Research), 1966-1985 (Box 83)
    - Presidents Council State Colleges and Universities, 1982-1984 (Box 83)
    - Primary Research, 1982-1984 (Box 83)
    - Program for Executive Exchange and Research, 1984 (Box 83)
    - Project Management Plan, 1983 (Box 83)
    - Protein Structure and Design, Program in, 1982-1984 (Box 83)
      (see Molecular Genetics)
    - Psychiatry, Department of, 1981-1984 (Box 83)
    - Psychology, Department of, 1982-1984 (Box 83)
    - Public Health, School of, 1982-1984 (Box 84)
    - Public Policy Studies, Institute of, 1982-1984 (Box 84)
    - Purchasing, 1981 (Box 84)
    - P General, 1982-1984 (Box 84)
    - Quality Assurance Unit, 1984 (Box 84)
    - Radiation Control Service, 1982-1984 (Box 84)
    - Radiation Policy Committee, 1981-1983; 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Radiology, Department of, 1983-1984 (Box 84)
    - Recreational Sports, Department of, 1981-1983 (Box 84)
    - Regents, 1981-1986
      - Annual Report to, 1983-1984 (Box 84)
      - Communications, 1982-1985 (Box 84)
      - Correspondence, 1981-1985; 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Reproductive Endocrinology, 1983-1984 (Box 84)
    - Research Advisory Council, 1975-1984 (Box 84)
    - Research Agenda, 1981-1983; 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Research Club, University of Michigan, 1980-1981 (Box 84)
    - Research Corporation, 1981-1982 (Box 84)
    - Research Development and Administration, Division of, 1980-1982 (Box 84)
    - Research Development and Administration, Division of, 1983-1984; 2 folders (Box 85)
    - Research Ethics, 1982 (Box 85)
    - Research Incentives Program, 1984 (Box 85)
    - Research, Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 85)
      (see MSA and Research Policies Committee)
    - Research News, 1982-1984 (Box 85)
    - Research Policies Committee, 1982-1985; 2 folders (Box 85)
    - Research Reporting, 1983 (Box 85)
    - Research Utilization of Scientific Knowledge, Center for, 1982-1984 (Box 85)
    - Research, Volume of, 1976-1984 (Box 85)
    - Residential College, 1982-1984 (Box 85)
    - Robotics, 1980-1982 (Box 85)
    - Robotics and Integrated Manufacturing, Center for (CRIM), 1982-1984 (Box 85)
    - Royalties, Distribution of, 1983-1984 (Box 85)
    - Russian and East European Studies, Center for, 1982-1984 (Box 85)
    - R General, 1982-1984 (Box 85)
    - Science and Technology, Institute of, 1981-1984
      - General, 1982-1984; 2 folders (Box 85)
      - Innovation and New Products Center, 1982-1984 (Box 85)
      - Management and Productivity, Center on, 1982 (Box 85)
      - Task Force, 1982-1983 (Box 85)
      - Ultra-Small Electronics Research (USER), 1983 (Box 85)
    - Scientists' Institute for Public Information, 1982-1983 (Box 85)
    - SCRIPT (Stanford Computerized Research Information Profile Technique), 1982-1984 (Box 85)
    - Searle Scholars Program, 1981-1986; 2 folders (Box 85)
    - Senate, United States, 1983-1984 (Box 85)
    - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA), 1982-1985 (Box 85)
    - Service Awards, 1982-1984 (Box 85)
    - Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society, 1983 (Box 85)
    - Signature Authorization, 1980-1984 (Box 86)
    - Simpson Memorial Institute, 1983 (Box 86)
    - Small Business Innovation Research, 1982-1984 (Box 86)
    - Social Organization, Center for Research on, 1982-1984 (Box 86)
    - Social Research, Institute for, 1979-1984
      - Financial Reports (Monthly and Annual), 1979-1984 (Box 86)
      - General File, 1982-1984; 2 folders (Box 86)
    - Social Science Association, Consortium of (COSSA), 1980-1982 (Box 86)
    - Social Work, School of, 1982-1984 (Box 86)
    - Society of Research Administrators, 1982 (Box 86)
    - Sociology, Department of, 1984 (Box 86)
    - Software Engineering Institute, 1983-1984; 2 folders (Box 86)
    - South and Southeast Asian Studies, Center for, 1983 (Box 86)
    - Space Physics Research Laboratory, 1980-1984 (Box 86)
    - Space, Problems of Limited Office and Research (Alpern and Schnitzer), 1982- (Box 86)
    - Space Science Working Group, 1982-1983 (Box 86)
    - Special Projects Division, 1984 (Box 86)
    - Spencer Foundation Advisory Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 86)
    - Standard Oil Company, 1983 (Box 86)
    - State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, National Association of, 1982-1984 (Box 86)
    - Statistical Research Laboratory, 1967-1985
      - Advisory Committee, 1984 (Box 86)
      - Fox, Daniel J., Royalty Payments to, 1985 (Box 86)
      - General Files, 1967-1984 (Box 86)
      - MIDAS Leasing Agreements, 1978-1984 (Box 86)
    - Statistical Analysis System (SAS), 1983-1984 (Box 86)
    - Strategic Wildland Management Studies, Center for, 1981-1984 (Box 86)
    - Students, 1981-1984 (Box 86)
    - Students, Minority, 1983 (Box 86)
    - Summer Appointments, 1981-1983 (Box 86)
    - Supercomputer, 1984 (Box 86)
    - Superconducting Supercollider, 1983-1984; 2 folders (Box 86)
      (See Megaproposals)
    - Surgery, Department of, 1982-1983 (Box 87)
    - Survey Research Center (ISR), 1982-1984 (Box 87)
    - S General, 1982-1984 (Box 87)
    - Telecommunications, 1981-1984 (Box 87)
    - Thurnau Trust, 1983-1984 (Box 87)
    - Travel, 1978-1984 (Box 87)
    - Turner Geriatric Clinic, 1979-1984 (Box 87)
    - T General, 1981-1984 (Box 87)
    - Ultra-Small Structures Research Office, 1982-1984 (Box 87)
    - United Way, 1981-1986; 3 folders (Box 87)
    - University Libraries, 1982-1984 (Box 87)
    - University of Michigan Transportation Research Institute (UMTRI), 1981-1985
      - General Files, 1982-1984 (Box 87)
      - Highway Safety Research Institute (previous name of UMTRI), 1982-1983 (Box 87)
      - Review Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 87)
    - University Research Association, 1981-1984 (Box 87)
    - Urban, Technological, and Environmental Planning, 1982-1983 (Box 87)
    - U General, 1982-1984 (Box 87)
    - Values and Science, Collegiate Institute for, 1982-1984 (Box 87)
    - Vice-President, 1982-1984
      - Academic Affairs, 1982-1984; 2 folders (Box 87)
      - Chief Financial Officer, 1982-1983 (Box 87)
      - Development and University Relations, 1982-1984 (Box 87)
      - Research, 1982-1984
        - Arts and Humanities Advisor, 1984 (Box 87)
        - Assistant (Alan Price), 1982-1984 (Box 87)
        - Deans, Directors, and Department Head Memos, 1983 (Box 87)
        - Federal Relations, 1982-1984 (Box 87)
        - General Files, 1982-1984 (Box 87)
        - Research on Merger with Graduate School, 1982-1984; 2 folders (Box 87)
        - Staff Meetings, 1983 (Box 87)
        - Subcommittee Assigned Rackham Review, 1982-1984 (Box 87)
      - State Relations and Secretary of the University, 1983-1984
        - Assistant (Tom Butts), 1983-1984 (Box 87)
    - Wang Wordprocesser, 1982-1984 (Box 87)
    - Warner-Lambert Company, 1982-1984 (Box 87)
    - Wolf Prize, 1982-1983 (Box 87)
    - Women, 1983-1984 (Box 87)
    - W General, 1982-1984 (Box 87)
    - Zoology, Museum of, 1983-1984 (Box 87)
- Linda S. Wilson
  The Linda S. Wilson series (boxes 88-96) consists of Topical Files created during her tenure as vice president from 1985 to 1989 (some files, however, date from 1981). The topical File is divided into two chronological spans, 1984-1990 (1990 accession) and 1980-1990 (1993 accession). Wilson continued to use the same file system originated by Overberger: a single alphabetical arrangement. Among the new files generated under Wilson are: the Conflict of Interest Task Force, concerning policy revision; the Gifts, Grants, and Contracts Committee Report, on how to accelerate and facilitate the process of identifying and reporting gift transfers to the university; International Peace and Security Research, concerning a new research center; Michigan Technology Transfer Network, on promoting the transfer of technical and business expertise to the business sector; the Research Excellence and Development Fund, on using state resources for job creation and economic revitalization in Michigan; New and Emerging Technology Task Force; and Radioactive Waste Disposal.
  Some of the larger groupings of continuing files for 1985 to 1989 are the Division of Research Administration and Development (administrative files), the Unit for Laboratory Animal Medicine, Electron Microbeam Analysis Laboratory, Macromolecular Research Center, Michigan Sea Grant College Program, and the Super Conducting Supercollider. There are also staff meeting agendas and minutes from 1985 to 1989.
  - Topical Files
    - 1984-1989
      - Academic Integrity, 1984-1986 (Box 88)
      - Academic Policy Group, 1986-1989 (Box 88)
      - Afroamerican and African Studies, Center for, 1985 (Box 88)
      - Alumni Research Advisory Committee, 1985 (Box 88)
      - American Universities, Association of (AAU), 1986 (Box 88)
      - Anatomy and Biological Science, Departments of, 1985-1986 (Box 88)
      - Anthropology, Museum of, 1983-1987 (Box 88)
      - Applied Physics Program, 1986 (Box 88)
      - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of, 1984-1987 (Box 88)
      - Argonne National Laboratory
        - 1985 (Box 88)
        - 1986 (Box 88)
      - Art, School of, 1987 (Box 88)
      - Astronomy, Department of, 1984-1985 (Box 88)
      - Atmospheric and Oceanic Sciences, Department of, 1985-1987 (Box 88)
      - Atmospheric Research, University Corporation (UCAR), 1985 (Box 88)
      - Automotive Industry Conference, 1985-1989 (Box 88)
      - Bid Protest, 1986-1989 (Box 88)
      - Biological Sciences, Division of, 1985-1986 (Box 88)
      - Biotechnology, 1989 (Box 88)
      - Botanical Gardens, 1985 (Box 88)
      - Burroughs Corporation, 1985 (Box 88)
      - Chemistry, Department of, 1985-1986 (Box 88)
      - China Automotive Project, 1986-1988 (Box 88)
      - Chinese Association of Science and Technology (Cast), 1986-1987 (Box 88)
      - Civil Engineering, Department of, 1986 (Box 88)
      - Computer Maintenance, 1985-1987 (Box 88)
      - Computing Center, 1985 (Box 88)
      - Conflict of Interest Task Force
        - 1981-1984 (Box 88)
        - 1984 (Box 88)
        - 1985 (Box 88)
      - Consortium of Private and Public Institutions, 1986 (Box 88)
      - Consumers Power, 1986 (Box 88)
      - Dearborn Campus, U-M, 1985-1986 (Box 88)
      - Dentistry, School of
        - General
          - 1984-1985 (Box 88)
          - 1986-1987 (Box 88)
          - 1988-1989 (Box 88)
        - Dental Research Institute Policy Committee, 1984-1989 (Box 88)
        - Geriatric Oral Science Center Policy Committee, 1988 (Box 88)
      - Diversity
        - Office of the Vice President Reporting Units Diversity Plans, 1987-1988 (Box 88)
        - Symposium and Initiatives Program, 1987-1989 (Box 88)
      - Dual career couples project, 1988-1989 (Box 88)
      - Economics, Department of, 1985-1986 (Box 88)
      - Economic Development, Center for Research on
        - General, 1989 (Box 88)
        - Budget Reviews, 1986 (Box 88)
      - Education, School of, 1985-1987 (Box 88)
      - Electron Microbeam Analysis Laboratory
        - General
          - 1985 (Box 89)
          - 1986, 2 folders (Box 89)
          - 1987 (Box 89)
      - Energy Department, 1983-1989 (Box 89)
      - Electronic Engineering and Computer Science, Department of, 1985-1986 (Box 89)
      - Engineering, College of
        - General
          - 1985, 2 folders (Box 89)
          - 1986 (Box 89)
          - 1987 (Box 89)
      - Engineering Research Center, 1987 (Box 89)
      - English Language and Literature, Department of
        - 1986 (Box 89)
        - 1988-1989 (Box 89)
      - English Language Institute, 1987 (Box 89)
      - Executive Officers, 1985-1989 (Box 89)
      - Export Administration Regulations, 1986 (Box 89)
      - Faculty Support Program, 1988 (Box 89)
      - Federal Government Relations Material
        - 1985 (Box 89)
        - 1986, 2 folders (Box 89)
        - 1987 (Box 89)
      - Flexible Benefits Program Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 89)
      - Ford Library Liaison Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 89)
      - Gas Research Institute, 1986 (Box 89)
      - General Counsel Activities, 1986-1987 (Box 89)
      - General Motors Academic Forum, 1985 (Box 89)
      - Geological Science, Department of, 1986-1988 (Box 89)
      - Geosciences Research, 1987-1988 (Box 89)
      - Gerontology, Institute of, 1984-1986 (Box 89)
      - Gifts, Grants, and Contracts Committee Report
        - 1985 (Box 89)
        - 1986 (Box 89)
        - 1987 (Box 89)
      - Girls and Science and Technology, 1985-1987 (Box 89)
      - Global Ecology and Change, 1988-1989 (Box 89)
      - Government, University, Industry, Research Roundtable, 1987 (Box 89)
      - Graduate School, Horace H. Rackham
        - 1985 (Box 89)
        - 1986 (Box 89)
        - 1987 (Box 89)
        - 1988-1989 (Box 89)
      - Gramm-Rudman (federal deficit reduction legislation)
        - 1985 (Box 89)
        - 1986 (Box 89)
      - Great Lakes and Aquatic Sciences, Center for (Box 90)
        - 1985-1986 (Box 90)
        - 1987-1988 (Box 90)
      - Great Lakes Research Division, 1985-1987 (Box 90)
      - Guidelines for Voluntary Support Transfers, 1987 (Box 90)
      - Hazardous Waste, Michigan Consortium, 1985-1987 (Box 90)
      - Higher Education Act, 1985 (Box 90)
      - Higher Education Coordinating Council, Michigan Strategic Fund Technology Strategy, 1986-1987 (Box 90)
      - Historically Black Colleges and University Advisory Committee, 1988 (Box 90)
      - Human Genetics, Department of, 1989 (Box 90)
      - Industrial Development Division, Institute of Science and Technology
        - 1986 (Box 90)
        - 1987 (Box 90)
      - Industrial Liaison, 1986 (Box 90)
      - Industrial Technology Institute, 1987-1989 (Box 90)
      - Institutional Goals, 1986-1987 (Box 90)
      - Interdisciplinary Research, 1987 (Box 90)
      - Internal Medicine
        - 1985 (Box 90)
        - 1986-1987 (Box 90)
      - International Activities, 1985-1986 (Box 90)
      - International Center, 1987-1988 (Box 90)
      - International Friendship Association, Tokyo, Japan, 1985 (Box 90)
      - International Peace and Security Research, Office of
        - 1986-1987 (Box 90)
        - 1988 (Box 90)
      - Kelsey Museum of Archaeology, 1985 (Box 90)